mp3suite.com 2012-05-22

# MP3Suite - Privacy Policy

**MP3 Suite Inc - Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that is collects when you agree to receive e-mail marketing from us or one of our affiliates. It is important that visitors are fully informed concerning the use of their personal information. We believe in 100% permission-based marketing.

You may unsubscribe from any of our or our affiliates e-mail marketing programs at any time. In every e-mail communication we send, you will find an unsubscribe hyperlink allowing the recipient the ability to unsubscribe from the specific marketing program by simply clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions that follow. We attempt to process all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion. However, after unsubscribing, we cannot guarantee that you will never receive another mailing from us, because we may obtain your e-mail address in the future through a different e-mail marketing program to which you have subscribed. However, we can guarantee that if you should ever receive another e-mail communication from us, you will be able to remove your e-mail address via the unsubscribe hyperlink.

Our company reserves the right to provide aggregate or group data about our users without disclosing personally identifiable information for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage, or characteristics of participants as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.

Additionally, when you open, preview or click on the advertising portion of our e-mails and/or those of our marketing partners and/or our affiliates, you have agreed to the terms set forth in our Privacy Policy and agree that as a function of opening, previewing or clicking on the advertising portion of our e-mails, that you will receive new or additional marketing communications from us, our marketing partners and/or our affiliates.

We also reserves the right to release current or past User information in the event that our company believes that the User is using, or has used, our services in violation of the terms and conditions, to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if our company is sold or acquired, or when we deem it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when our company, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate.

It is our goal to safeguard and protect our Users information. When Users submit information at the website, their information is protected both online and off-line. The privacy of your personal information is very important to us. Our employees are committed to our privacy and security policies.

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any website by those who are under 18 years of age without the prior consent of their parent or guardian. Notwithstanding the foregoing, children 18 years of age and younger are not permitted to access this website and we do not knowingly collect personal information from such children. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

Users may receive e-mail verifying their registration with this site as well as promotional marketing of commercial products and services.

Our company does not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of each of the advertisers and/or third parties accessible through this website.

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on our website. We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may share it with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

Your Acceptance of These Terms by using this site, including, without limitation, signing up for offers and/or continuing to receive information from us, you agree to the our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this website. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website or acceptance of our emails following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving emails from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not register on this site.

_Revised 08-08-2008_
